<words>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Cat</name>
        <description>A small domesticated carnivorous mammal with soft fur, a short snout, and retractable claws.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Dog</name>
        <description>A domesticated carnivorous mammal that typically has a long snout, an acute sense of smell, and is often kept as a pet or working animal.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Sun</name>
        <description>The star around which the Earth orbits, providing light and heat to the planet.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Run</name>
        <description>To move rapidly on foot; to sprint or jog.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Hat</name>
        <description>A covering for the head, typically with a brim and a crown.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Red</name>
        <description>A color at the end of the spectrum next to orange and opposite violet, as the color of blood, fire, or rubies.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Book</name>
        <description>A written or printed work consisting of pages glued or sewn together along one side and bound in covers.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Tree</name>
        <description>A woody perennial plant, typically having a single main stem or trunk, supporting branches and leaves.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Ball</name>
        <description>A round or spherical object used in various sports and games.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Jump</name>
        <description>To propel oneself upwards or forwards into the air, using one's feet and legs.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Milk</name>
        <description>A white liquid produced by mammary glands of mammals, often consumed as a beverage.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Rain</name>
        <description>Precipitation in the form of liquid water droplets that fall from the atmosphere.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Blue</name>
        <description>A color resembling the clear sky on a sunny day.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Fish</name>
        <description>A limbless cold-blooded vertebrate animal with gills and fins, living wholly in water.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Duck</name>
        <description>A waterbird with a broad flat bill, webbed feet, and a quack sound.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Ship</name>
        <description>A large watercraft for transporting goods or passengers by sea.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Face</name>
        <description>The front part of a person's head, from the forehead to the chin, or the corresponding part in an animal.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Smile</name>
        <description>A pleased, kind, or amused facial expression, typically with the corners of the mouth turned up and the front teeth exposed.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Wind</name>
        <description>The natural movement of the air, especially in the form of a current of air blowing from a particular direction.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Frog</name>
        <description>An amphibian with a short squat body, moist skin, and long hind legs for leaping.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Cake</name>
        <description>A sweet baked food made from a mixture of flour, sugar, eggs, and other ingredients, usually with icing on top.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Star</name>
        <description>A luminous point in the night sky that is a large, remote incandescent body like the sun.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Moon</name>
        <description>The natural satellite of the Earth, visible by reflection of sunlight and appearing as a shining disk in the night sky.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Bird</name>
        <description>A warm-blooded egg-laying vertebrate with feathers, wings, and a beak.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Snow</name>
        <description>Atmospheric water vapor frozen into ice crystals and falling in light white flakes or lying on the ground as a white layer.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Door</name>
        <description>A hinged, sliding, or revolving barrier at the entrance to a building, room, or vehicle, or in the framework of a cupboard.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Song</name>
        <description>A musical composition with lyrics for voice or voices, performed by singing.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Frog</name>
        <description>An amphibian with a short squat body, moist skin, and long hind legs for leaping.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Leaf</name>
        <description>The flattened structure of a higher plant, typically green and blade-like, that is attached to a stem directly or via a stalk.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>King</name>
        <description>A male ruler of an independent state, especially one who inherits the position by right of birth.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Nest</name>
        <description>A structure or place made or chosen by a bird for laying eggs and sheltering its young.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Ant</name>
        <description>A small insect, often with a sting, that usually lives in a complex social colony with one or more breeding queens.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Bear</name>
        <description>A large, heavy mammal with thick fur and a short tail, including the polar bear, brown bear, and black bear.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Egg</name>
        <description>The rounded reproductive body produced by the female of certain animals, consisting of an ovum surrounded by layers of membranes and an outer casing.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Fire</name>
        <description>The process of combustion manifested in light, flame, and heat.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Goat</name>
        <description>A domesticated ruminant mammal with backward-curving horns, related to the sheep and capable of producing milk.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>House</name>
        <description>A building for human habitation, especially one that is lived in by a family or small group of people.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Juice</name>
        <description>The liquid obtained from or present in fruit or vegetables.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Lamp</name>
        <description>A device for giving light, consisting of a source of illumination and a glass or transparent cover that encloses the light source.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Park</name>
        <description>A large public green area in a town, used for recreation.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Queen</name>
        <description>A female ruler of an independent state, especially one who inherits the position by right of birth.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Rock</name>
        <description>A large rugged mass of hard mineral material or stone.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Seed</name>
        <description>The mature fertilized ovule of a flowering plant, capable of developing into another such plant.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Tiger</name>
        <description>A large carnivorous feline mammal with a yellowish-brown coat striped with black.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Water</name>
        <description>A colorless, transparent, odorless, and tasteless liquid that forms the seas, lakes, rivers, and rain.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Zoo</name>
        <description>An establishment that maintains a collection of wild animals, typically in a park or gardens, for study, conservation, or display to the public.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Apple</name>
        <description>A round fruit with red or green skin and a whitish interior.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Candy</name>
        <description>Sweet food made with sugar or syrup combined with fruit, chocolate, or nuts.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Farm</name>
        <description>An area of land and its buildings used for growing crops and rearing animals.</description>
    </word>
    <word difficulty="easy">
        <name>Joke</name>
        <description>A form of entertainment, consisting of typically humorous remarks, intended to make an audience laugh.</description>
    </word>
</words>
